DODONG-RI VARIETY SHOP
SAMBO FISH TAEPYEONG BUILDING
WHEN LIFE GIVES YOU TANGERINES
GEUM EUN DONG'S DINER SBS LIVE TODAY
A SPECIAL SEAFOOD RESTAURANT
IN JEJU THAT SBS FOUND
AIRS ON APRIL 22, 2004
TV DRAMA "ALL-IN", HOT SPOT RESTAURANT
ON SCENIC ROUTE FOR TOURISTS
IC CREDIT CARD PURCHASE
PAYMENT APPROVED
FRESH FISH FOR TAKEOUT
COME ON IN GROUPS WELCOME,
BANQUET SEATING AVAILABLE
HANDMADE DUMPLINGS IN CRISIS
OUR SON, HIS WIFE, AND THEIR CHILDREN
ALL EAT HERE
DINE-IN CUSTOMERS
UNLIMITED REFILL OF SQUID SOUP
JEJU BLACK PIG, COME ON IN
PHONE 872-5247, 2F
RED MANGO
START LOVING YOURSELF
LIVE SQUID, SEAFOOD RESTAURANT
GEUM EUN DONG'S DINER
ARIRANG, HANDMADE, 2F
KALGUKSU, SUJEBI, SAMGYETANG
COFFEE & HOF
CITY POP
BADANG RED BEAN PORRIDGE
JEJU'S SPECIALTY
THE ORIGINAL SQUID RESTAURANT
JEJU HOT SPOT
SQUID…
DDUKBAEGI SQUID SOUP, 4000 WON
SOFT, LOUD
GEUM-MYEONG - GINGER TEA, TWICE A DAY
SAE-BOM - CHOPPED VEGGIES, FREEZER
CHUNG-SEOB - BLACK GARLIC, PATIO
CHECK IN, APPOINTMENTS
PREPARING FOR AN ENDOSCOPY
ENDOSCOPY CENTER, ELECTROCARDIOGRAM
LAB, PULMONARY FUNCTION LAB
ENDOSCOPY ROOM, RECOVERY ROOM,
GEOSAN GENERAL HOSPITAL
WANGGGUMTUELI, CARAMEL,
LONGDAELONG, KANCHO
DILIGENCE, FIDELITY, COOPERATION
LET'S LEARN, NAME: YANG DONG-MYEONG
DODONG-RI VARIETY SHOP
THE MOST ADORABLE UNCLE
CROW, CRAB, SNOT-NOSE,
MISCHIEVOUS BOY
FOAL, PUPPY, OUR YOUNGEST, OUR BABY
DONG-MYEONG, SO MANY NICKNAMES
COULD HAVE BEEN GIVEN TO OUR LITTLE BABY
WE BURIED HIM IN OUR HEARTS
WE HAD HIM HIDDEN DEEP WITHIN
A BROTHER, A COLLEAGUE, I TOOK AWAY THE
CHANCE FOR HIM TO BE CALLED THOSE NAMES
OUR GRANDCHILDREN SAY "UNCLE DONG-MYEONG"
WHERE THEIR UNCLE LAY
THE STONE WALL THAT WE BUILT INSIDE OUR
HEARTS HAVE BEEN COMPLETELY CRUMBLED
A THREE-YEAR-OLD UNCLE, DONG-MYEONG
MY THREE-YEAR-OLD BABY
PLAQUE OF APPRECIATION, YANG GWAN-SIK,
GEUM EUN DONG'S DINER
PLAQUE OF GRATITUDE
YANG GWAN-SIK, OSUN-EUB DODONG-RI
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
OH AE-SUN, DODONG FISHING VILLAGE CHIEF
ADMISSIONS RECEPTION, PAYMENT
EXPERIMENTAL MEDICINE, BLOOD TEST ROOM
RESOURCE ROOM
PLEASE PLACE YOUR PATIENT FILE
IN ORDER AND WAIT A MOMENT.
RECEPTION
WHITE RICE? BROWN RICE?
HOW MUCH SHOULD HE EXERCISE?
CAN HE GET FLU SHOTS?
WHAT ABOUT MOXIBUSTION?
PORK? BEEF? GOOD
GENERAL INFORMATION REGARDING
CHECKUP NAME: JANG SUN-RYE
REGISTRATION NUMBER: 851
PEOPLE IN WAITING: 7
PUBLIC PHONE
ESTABLISHING ADVANCED ORDER
DAECHI POLICE STATION
CHINESE CUISINE
FLYING ROBOT Z-MAN
FLYING SPACE WARRIOR
BABAOCAI, NAENGMYEON,
SOJU, BEER, KAOLIANG LIQUOR
CELEBRITY LECTURERS CONFERENCE
HAN SEUNG-JIN, MATH LECTURER
TODAY'S CELEBRITY LECTURER
YANG GEUM-MYEONG, CEO
YANG GEUM-MYEONG
CEO OF EVER STUDY
CELEBRITY LECTURERS CONFERENCE
YANG GEUM-MYEONG
W EVER STUDY
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE OPENING
OF THE JEJU HAENYEO MUSEUM
JULY 1, 2006 JEJU PROVINCE
POSITIVE THINKING
CERTIFICATE OF ADMISSION, DIRECTOR
OF ADMISSIONS, SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY
CALLING PARK TOTO
2007 COLLEGE SCHOLASTIC ABILITY TEST
SEOUL METROPOLITAN OFFICE OF EDUCATION,
REGION 18, TEST SITE 6
YEOUIDO HIGH SCHOOL
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
ISOLATION ROOM
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
RESTRICTED AREA GEOSAN GENERAL HOSPITAL
YANG GWAN-SIK, HANIL BANK
AMOUNT, DEPOSIT, WITHDRAWAL
ACCOUNT NUMBER, 486-072200-01-131
PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE FROM HOSPITAL
OR CLINIC, MR. YANG GWAN-SIK
SEEING YOUR LOVE LEAVE IN THE MORNING AND
COME HOME THROUGH THE SAME DOOR AT NIGHT
WAS AN EVERYDAY MIRACLE
OH AE-SUN
JEONG GONG-RYE I'VE BEEN EMBARRASSED MY
WHOLE LIFE BECAUSE I DIDN'T GO TO SCHOOL
IF ANYONE ASKED ME WHAT I WANTED TO ORDER,
MY HEART SANK EVERY TIME.
BUT YESTERDAY, I ORDERED WHAT I WANTED
TO EAT ALL BY MYSELF.
I ORDERED A BIG PLATE OF SUSHI,
IT WAS THE BEST THING I EVER HAD
MY DAUGHTER
BEST SQUID SOUP IN THE NATION
GEUM EUN DONG'S DINER
MY LITTLE HERO, LA CONCERT LIVE
WITH HER FINE, FAIR HAND
I FAINTLY REMEMBER
WHEN OUR YOUNGEST BOY WAS
STUDYING FOR COLLEGE
LET'S GO TOGETHER, TOGETHER
FEBRUARY 24, 2024, 6 P.M.
JEJU HAENYEO MUSEUM
EXPRESS DELIVERY BADANG GGOT PRESS
HERE'S TO ALL YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
OH AE-SUN
DEDICATION
I SHED TEARS READING THIS STORY, AS ITS
BEAUTY HAD A DREAM-LIKE QUALITY TO IT.
"I'M SORRY, THANK YOU. I LOVE YOU"
EDITOR-IN-CHIEF, BADANG GGOT
MATERIAL MEANS
37 VOTES FOR OH AE-SUN, 28 FOR LEE MAN-GI
STILL CAN'T FORGET THOSE NUMBERS, HEARING
THE WRESTLING CHAMPION'S NAME WAS PAINFUL
I LOST THE PRESIDENCY TO GENERAL'S SON
BECAUSE MY MOM DIDN’T HAVE MATERIAL MEANS
MY YOUNG HEART SWALLOWED A HOT COAL
THE 300-YEAR EXPLORATION OF EVOLUTION
CHANGE BOOK
LANGUEDOC WHERE YOU CAN PLACE
BEAUTIFUL RED HEARTS
LITTLE RUNT
HE'S A HANDSPAN SHORTER THAN I AM
HE SAYS HE'S OLDER
THAT LITTLE RUNT
KEEPS FOLLOWING ME AROUND
THE DAY THAT WE BECAME THE SAME AGE
THE DAY I LOST MY MOTHER I TURNED TEN,
I BECAME AN ORPHAN WHEN I WAS TEN
IT'S SAD THAT I PLOWED THAT TINY FIELD
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER THAN MY GRANDSON
BUT IT WAS NOTHING COMPARED
TO WHAT MY MOTHER HAD TO GO THROUGH
MY MOTHER LEFT BEHIND THREE CHILDREN
WHEN SHE WAS TWENTY-NINE
SHE WAS TWENTY-NINE
WHEN I TURNED TWENTY-NINE,
I CRIED LIKE I WAS TEN AGAIN
TABLE OF CONTENTS
ACT 1, HOW QUICKLY TIME FLIES
AS SPRING PASSES BY
ACT 2, EXTREME HEAT, TYPHOON,
FIRST TIME FOR EVERYTHING
BY THE SPEED OF SUMMER
ACT 3, IT WASN'T A SEASON OF HARVEST
BUT A SEASON OF EMPTY POCKETS
FALL BEARS ALL KINDS OF FRUIT
ACT 4, STILL SHINING ON
THE SPARK OF WINTER
CONGRATULATIONS, DODONG-RI
VILLAGE CHIEF OH AE-SUN
OH AE-SUN